Tell me how you think I'm wrong When I say I feel so lost
Tell me why you think you're love Be erased or let it cost
Tell me why you look at me Like I'm just a piece of dust
Tell me how you think you know When I give away my trust
Tell me how I'm
Let's see what's a hate watchers in here already
It's funny like
You know I've been around like a lot of people in like business and people live with jobs and people would go
There's people that make money in different ways, and it's like it's no it's no it's okay
It's no it's never a problem. I never see anybody else having a problem even criminals
Like if there's nobody even criticizing these criminals. Oh stealing million. Oh, man
The person deserves it. You know, it's like always
Even criminals are criticized less than I'm criticized about
Having ideas for my ship running my show like I want to oh
And it's like, but it's really annoying as like I'm being misrepresented so highly. It's like
It's just like common knowledge. Oh, you have to pay to get on my show. You have to pay
I don't think I've ever charged in the even an individual maybe in joking jokingly
I just you know, you know, oh, you know or not even jokingly if they would have you know
Some people I just want to talk to it's been it's my show. I've been allowed to talk to I want to talk to I can monetize
That's how I want you to
but it's like
Oh, well, you know, it's just common knowledge that I'm charging people to watch the show.
I mean, the show's free, right?
It is freedom.
I don't care about people's opinions of me either, but it's like at a point where it's
like it's just a being misrepresented.
As like this common knowledge and then it's like and then it hurts my business where it's like no one wants to buy by any
Readings from me. No one even wants to support the show anymore in any way, right?
I think of myself that too, but it's like when I'm sitting here hungry and starving because you know, nobody is you know
Pit patronizing me anymore because people are just slandering me constantly
Then it pisses me off
Or when people say oh, yeah, I'm going I'm gonna I'll this day
I'm gonna I'm gonna book a I'm gonna book a reading with you and say if you don't want to book a reading
You don't ever have to but if you like if you say you're going to I
appreciate
I mean I consider that like you know someone say hey look like a
Agreement almost you know at that point, but that it didn't when it's not and then there is like when people like we're not even considering
Like you're doing that they're just like playing with me in a way like that's
That is that like how you treat people I don't know
Yeah, but I'm not really in the mood to smile anymore because like now it's like now it's like I'm harming my survival
It's not funny. It's not it's it's not funny to me. It's not like
See a one person talking to me in here. I'll sleep this dream because there's just hate watchers
You see it's just pure people hate watchers not one person saying hi except miss Liz
Out of ten people. That's like 90% of people coming here. They hate me
That's not a good feeling while 40 people but before people talking 1% well
I'm 10% of people or one person in 10
Will even talk to me in here or unless or they know there's not there shouldn't talk because they can't say anything nice
Oh, yeah, I know I know but it's like I can't I wish I could deal with I can wish I could be like that where it's like
Oh, I don't care what people say or do or think but when it comes to having a business
you do start to care because
It's slanderous. It is absolutely slanderous
It's like
It's not it's not true. It's not fair. It's not right. I know
And it's like, but it's like so,
I just don't see people getting so disrespected.
And is it like just me?
Is it like, am I just like,
oh, it's just like I deserve to be disrespected
or it's like, I'm just like a bad person because of what?
What I say, I still don't like kind of understand why I've hated so much or even if not hated
Oh, we're just here to laugh at you. You're just like, you know, it's worthless
Low-cow we're trying to like, you know, you're just you're just you're just here to like make us laugh until I know at you
Right at you until
You know, basically you on the live yourself and then we'll go to the next person. That's what we do. That's that's like the goal, right?
And that's pretty big goal. That's why I'm like very sensitive to the SUIC IDE stuff
How many people here have told me go unalive myself
View
More than normal normal should be
told me
Maybe people will hear that maybe once in their lifetime, but not constantly I guess
Hi, hi, hi, hi
So anyway, what I'm thinking
And it's like what I mean, this was this this is just making it worse at this point
It's like what addressing it or like but I do have to express myself and it
But yeah, see nobody cares anymore like Liz dangle here. Thank you so much for coming
But I'm just gonna delete this and maybe not come back for a while. Bye